Learning Journal Unit 4

Part 1

Section 6.2 of your textbook describes incremental development. Do the exercise at the end of that section:

As an exercise, use incremental development to write a function called hypotenuse that returns the length of the hypotenuse of a right triangle given the lengths of the other two legs as arguments. Record each stage of the development process as you go. (Downey, 2015)

After the final stage of development, print the output of hypotenuse(3, 4) and two other calls to hypotenuse with different arguments.

Include all of the following in your Learning Journal:

An explanation of each stage of development, including code and any test input and output.
The output of hypotenuse(3,4).
The output of two additional calls to hypotenuse with different arguments.

Part 2

Invent your own function that does some useful computation of your choosing. Do not copy the function from somewhere else. Use incremental development, and record each stage of the development process as you go. Finally, print output that demonstrates that the function works as you intended.

Include all of the following in your Learning Journal:

An explanation of each stage of development, including code and any test input and output.
The output of three calls to your function with different arguments.

Part 3

Describe your experience so far with peer assessment of Discussion Assignments.

How do you feel about the feedback and ratings you have received from your peers?
How do you think your peers feel about the feedback you provided them? And the ratings you gave them?