Learning Journal Unit 2

Part 1:

The volume of a sphere is 4/3πr3, where π has the value of "pi" given in Section 2.1 of your textbook. Write a function called print_volume (r) that takes an argument for the radius of the sphere, and prints the volume of the sphere.

Call your print_volume function three times with different values for radius.

Include all of the following in your Learning Journal:

The code for your print_volume function.
The inputs and outputs to three calls of your print_volume.

Part 2:

Write your own function that illustrates a feature that you learned in this unit. The function must take at least one argument. The function should be your own creation, not copied from any other source. Do not copy a function from your textbook or the Internet.

Include all of the following in your Learning Journal:

The code for the function that you invented.
The inputs and outputs to three calls of your invented function.
A description of what feature(s) your function illustrates.  